<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on AAU Social Data Science Deep Learning - 2019 Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on AAU Social Data Science Deep Learning - 2019 Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AI in the workplace - Spoke the help bot</title>
      <link>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/spoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/spoke/</guid>
      <description>A short article about how the AI help bot, &amp;ldquo;Spoke&amp;quot;, can be used in workplace and hereby the HR department in a company.
Sources:
askspoke.com - 21 Ways AI Is Transforming the Workplace in 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approximate Nearest Neighbors Oh Yeah (ANNOY)</title>
      <link>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/ann/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/ann/</guid>
      <description>What is ANNOY ANNOY (Approximate Nearest Neighbors Oh Yeah) is a C++ library with Python bindings to search for points in space that are close to a given query point eg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deconvolution and Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/deconvolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/deconvolution/</guid>
      <description>Group members: Johannes Hoseth, Sergiu Ropota, Katharina Granberg
Deconvolution - A Way Of Increasing Output Size Within the field of computer vision, a well-known and multi-faceted area is segmentation, i.e. identifying and classifying objects in an image, via classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image classification with ResNet50</title>
      <link>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/resnet50/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/resnet50/</guid>
      <description>Doing cool things with data doesn&#39;t always need to be difficult. By using ResNet-50 you don&#39;t have to start from scratch when it comes to building a classifier model and make a prediction based on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LipNet</title>
      <link>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/lipnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sds-aau.github.io/M3Port19/portfolio/lipnet/</guid>
      <description>Introduction LipNet is a neural network architecture for lipreading, it differs from earlier research within the field, because it maps whole sentences instead of detecting individual words or phoneme’s classification [1] (“A phoneme is the smallest unit of sound in a word that makes a difference in its pronunciation, as well as its meaning, from another word”[2]).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>